<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="UnusedResources">
    <string name="uc_my_latitude">Last known location - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_my_longitude">Last known location - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_my_altitude">Last known location - Altitude value (in m). If [hasAltitude] is false, 0.0f is returned</string>
    <string name="uc_my_accuracy">Last known location - Accuracy of the fix (in m). If hasAccuracy() is false, 0.0 is returned</string>
    <string name="uc_my_gps_fix">Last known location - UTC time of this location (in ms)</string>
    <string name="uc_my_speed">Speed of the device in meters/second. If [hasSpeed] is \'false\', 0.0f is returned.</string>
    <string name="uc_sensor_hrm">Heart rate value in BMP. If hasSensorHeartRate() is false, 0.0 is returned.</string>
    <string name="uc_sensor_cadence">Cadence value. If hasCadence() is false, 0 is returned.</string>
    <string name="uc_sensor_speed">Speed of the device over ground in meters/second. This speed is defined only when \'speed sensor\' is connected and supply valid values. If [hasSensorSpeed] is \'false\', 0.0f is returned (in m/s).</string>
    <string name="uc_sensor_strides">The num of strides. If hasSensorStrides() is false, 0 is returned.</string>
    <string name="uc_sensor_temperature">Temperature value. If hasSensorTemperature() is false, 0.0f is returned.</string>
    <string name="uc_pace">Current users pace value (min / km). Computed pace is from highly filtered speed, not from real speed included in current my location object.</string>
    <string name="uc_speed_vertical">Vertical speed from last few (around 5) seconds of enabled GPS\n@return vertical speed in m/s</string>
    <string name="uc_slope">Current (little filtered) slope value. More about slope, for example at http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slope)\n@return slope in 0.01%</string>
    <string name="uc_is_gps_valid">Information if current location is valid GPS location with usable accuracy (GPS has correctly computed "fix" value).</string>
    <string name="uc_gps_sat_used">Number of used satellites for GPS fix.</string>
    <string name="uc_gps_sat_all">Total number of visible satellites.</string>
    <string name="uc_declination">Current declination computed from a) current GPS location, or b) last known location Locus app knows.</string>
    <string name="uc_heading">Current device orientation. Source for value depend on settings in Locus. Also this value will be 0 in case, user do not need orientation for any action.\n@return orientation value (in degrees) or 0 if orientation is not used or known</string>
    <string name="uc_gps_angle">Angle between GPS shift and current orientation. This values differ from 0 based on current outside conditions\n@return angle (in degrees) or 0 if no shift exists or GPS or sensors are disabled</string>
    <string name="uc_course">Current device course. Source for this value is change in coordinates, or directly GPS values.\n@return course value (in degrees) or 0 if course is not known</string>
    <string name="uc_roll">Roll angle of current device. For more info see http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flight_dynamics\n@return roll angle (in degree) or 0 if not known</string>
    <string name="uc_pitch">Pitch angle of current device. For more info see http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flight_dynamics\n@return pitch angle (in degree) or 0 if not known</string>
    <string name="uc_is_user_touching">Indicate if user is currently touching a map screen. It do not indicate which specific action is doing, only that something is happening.</string>
    <string name="uc_is_guide_enabled">Flag is guidance is enabled.\n@return `true` if guiding is enabled</string>
    <string name="uc_is_track_rec_recording">Flag if track recording is currently active. It do not info about it\'s state (paused, running), just if it is enabled at all.\n@return `true` if track recording is active</string>
    <string name="uc_is_track_rec_paused">Flag if track recording is currently active or paused. Firstly check if recording is running before testing if is paused.\n@return `true` if track recording is paused</string>
    <string name="uc_track_rec_profile">Name of the active recording profile.\n@return profile name</string>
    <string name="uc_is_enabled_my_location">Flag if GPS is currently enabled in Locus.</string>
    <string name="uc_is_map_visible">Flag if some screen with map is currently visible\n@return `true` if map is visible</string>
    <string name="uc_active_live_track_id">ID of active running Live tracking.</string>
    <string name="uc_active_dashboard_id">ID of active visible dashboard.</string>
    <string name="uc_map_zoom_level">Current map zoom level. This value should not be precise in case of using custom map projections, anyway it\'s always closest possible value.\n@return integer as a current zoom level (zoom 0 == whole world (1 tile 256x256px))</string>
    <string name="uc_map_distance_to_gps">Returns the approximate distance in meters between Last known location and the map location. Distance is defined using the WGS84 ellipsoid.\n@return the approximate distance in meters</string>
    <string name="uc_map_rotate_angle">Current rotation value of map screen. This value may be same as current orientation or should be value by user manual rotation\n@return angle (in degrees) as map rotate</string>
    <string name="uc_map_bottom_right_lon">Bottom-right coordinate of current map screen\n@return max bottom-right visible location - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_map_bottom_right_lat">Bottom-right coordinate of current map screen\n@return max bottom-right visible location - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_map_top_left_lon">Top-left coordinate of current map screen\n@return max top-left visible location - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_map_top_left_lat">Top-left coordinate of current map screen\n@return max top-left visible location - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_map_center_lon">Even if map is visible or not, this define current map center.\n@return current map center - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_map_center_lat">Even if map is visible or not, this define current map center.\n@return current map center - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_total_length">Total length of done route (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_total_length_move">Total track distance with speed sensor value (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_neg_length">Negative grade (distance)</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_pos_length">Positive grade (distance)</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_neutral_length">Neutral grade (distance) (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_neutral_height">Neutral grade (elevation) (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_downhill">Negative grade (elevation)</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_eleva_uphill">Positive grade (elevation)</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_altitude_min">Minimum altitude on the track (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_altitude_max">Maximum altitude on the track (in m).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_start_time">Track start time (time of first point) (in ms).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_stop_time">Track stop time (time of last point) (in ms).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_time">Total time of route (in ms).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_time_move">Total track time with speed (in ms).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_speed_max">Maximal speed of this route (in m/s).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_average_speed_total">Get average speed value for a track including breaks\n@return average speed in m/s</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_average_speed_move">Get average speed value for a track only movement\n@return average speed in m/s</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_point_count">Number of points (useful when points itself are not loaded).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_cadence_avg">Get average value of cadence.\n@return average cadence value</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_cadence_max">Maximum cadence value.</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_energy_burned">Burned energy (in joule).</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_hrm_avg">Average value of heart rate.</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_hrm_max">Maximum HRM value.</string>
    <string name="uc_rec_strides_count">Total number of strides.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_lon">Current guiding location - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_lat">Current guiding location - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_angle">Bearing to target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_azimuth">Azimuth to target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_dist">Distance to target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_name">Name of guiding target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_time">Expected time to target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_dist_from_start">Distance from start (in case of guiding along track).</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_dist_to_finish">Distance to finish (in case of guiding along track).</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_target_id">ID of current target.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_time_to_finish">Expected time to finish (in case of guiding along track).</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_type">Get current guiding type.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_valid">Flag if active track guidance is valid.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_action">Action that happen on current navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_dist">Distance to current navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_extra">Extra information for navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_lon">Location of current navigation point - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_lat">Location of current navigation point - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_name">Name of current navigation target point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint1_time">Time to current navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_action">Action that happen on next navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_dist">Distance to next navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_extra">Extra information for navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_lon">Location of next navigation point - Longitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_lat">Location of next navigation point - Latitude in WGS coordinates</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_name">Name of next navigation target point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_navpoint2_time">Time to next navigation point.</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_nextvia_dist">Distance to the next via-point (or destination in case, no other via points exists).</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_nextvia_name">Name of the next via-point (or destination in case, no other via points exists).</string>
    <string name="uc_guide_nextvia_time">Relative time to the next via-point (or destination in case, no other via points exists).</string>
    <string name="uc_calc_remain_uphill_elevation">Remaining uphill elevation based on altitude values of each track point. Accuracy is dependent on the amount and quality of track point altitude values. Only available during Navigation based on an existing track.</string>
    <string name="uc_calc_remain_downhill_elevation">Remaining downhill elevation based on altitude values of each track point. Accuracy is dependent on the amount and quality of track point altitude values. Only available during Navigation based on an existing track.</string>
    <string name="uc_navigation_point_index">Index of nearest Point of the current navigation track. Only available during Navigation based on an existing track.</string>
    <string name="uc_navigation_track_name">Name of Track which is used for Navigation. Only available during Navigation based on an existing track.</string>
</resources>